[Music]
[音乐]
yes oh no we can stop yes thanks for
是的，哦，不，我们可以阻止是的，谢谢
thanks first things first
首先感谢第一件事
right so welcome everybody to this
对，所以欢迎大家
presentation how to live in a post
演示如何生活在帖子中
spring cloud netflix world thanks for
spring-cloud-netflix世界谢谢
coming we love your enthusiasm we can
来吧，我们爱您的热情，我们可以
see that you know you're plenty of
看到你知道你有很多
energy that's the most important thing
能量是最重要的
so it was a party yesterday
所以昨天是聚会
oh yeah we were at the party action so
哦，是的，我们参加了聚会
um we have quite a few quite a few
嗯，我们有很多
things to talk about so let's just waste
要谈论的事情，所以让我们浪费
some time right let's waste some time on
正确的时间，让我们浪费一些时间
talking about ourselves
谈论自己
so maybe okay my name is Olga Matuschek
所以也许好吧，我叫奥尔加·马图切克
Sharma you can find my Twitter handle
夏尔马你可以找到我的Twitter句柄
here if it's easier than the full name
如果比全名更容易
and I work in this print cloud team I
我在这个印刷云团队工作
mostly work on sprinkler contract but I
大多数工作在洒水合同上，但我
also do changes and work on gateway
也进行更改并在网关上工作
Netflix open thing yep so my name is
Netflix没错，所以我叫
Mockingjay Chuck and I'm working at the
Mockingjay Chuck和我在
spiracle team leading the slough and
灵动的团队领导着蜕
contract projects also I'm very fond of
合同项目我也很喜欢
CICE topics my twitter handle is that
我的Twitter处理的CICE主题是
i'm sure i can you can find my blog at
我确定我可以在以下位置找到我的博客
too much coding calm so a little bit of
太多的编码平静，所以一点点
history I guess so let's go back in time
历史，我想让我们回到过去
and let's say some five years or so so
假设大约五年左右
back in the days it sounds terrible like
回到过去，听起来就像
back in the days yeah yeah I remember
回想过去，是的，我记得
that five years ago we are at the time
五年前的我们
of course none of you were at this
当然你们都不在这
position but we had the problem with
位置，但我们遇到了问题
writing monoliths we're like we're
写巨石，我们就像我们
terrible at it absolutely bad they
他们非常糟糕，这很糟糕
didn't work so for some reason someone
由于某种原因没有工作
came to the conclusion that we can't
得出结论，我们不能
write good monoliths
写好巨石
so let's write distributed systems we
让我们来编写分布式系统
went to many conferences and there they
去了很多会议，在那里
told us that what you need to do now is
告诉我们您现在需要做的是
write distributed systems and it makes
写分布式系统，它使
perfect sense right you can't write a
完美的感觉吧，你不能写一个
single application with one transaction
一次交易的单一申请
distributed okay so we went to this
分布好，所以我们去了
conference and we say that's brilliant
会议，我们说那很棒
that sounds like a great idea so there
听起来不错，
are plenty of people doing presentations
很多人在做演示
on
上
to do micro-services right so you're
做正确的微服务，所以你
listening to those and we thought okay
听那些，我们认为还可以
let's go back to our company because
让我们回到我们的公司，因为
we've all got five years ago we work
我们已经有五年了
together in a single in an interesting
一起在一个有趣的
company and we started to think like
公司，我们开始想像
okay we have a monolithic application
好吧，我们有一个整体的应用程序
there as well so what kind of a problem
还有什么问题
would microservices solve for us so
微服务会为我们解决吗
we're thinking that um in general we do
我们认为总体上我们会
have a problem that the micro services
有一个问题，微服务
could solve which is the problem of
可以解决的是
scaling the app but not in terms of the
扩展应用程序，但不扩展
instance but having a lot of people
实例但是有很多人
working on a single codebase and also
在单个代码库上工作
the problem of not being hip enough oh
不够臀部的问题哦
that's yeah because you have to do micro
是的，因为你必须做微
services then you can hire people right
服务，然后您就可以雇用人员了
so we came to the conclusion that we
所以我们得出的结论是
can't have more people cuz we had over
不能有更多的人，因为我们已经结束了
100 people working on a single codebase
单个代码库上有100个人
back then and we talked to the business
那时，我们与企业进行了交谈
that you know we have problems we can't
你知道我们有问题，我们不能
actually you know deliver as many
实际上，您知道交付多少
features as you would like us to do
您希望我们做的功能
because we have too many people working
因为我们有太多人在工作
on the codebase so what's the absolutely
在代码库上，那么绝对是什么
greatest idea to solve this problem by
解决这个问题的好主意
the business obviously adding more
该业务显然增加了更多
people right so we had 120 people at
人们对，所以我们有120个人
some time and the velocity was even
一段时间，速度甚至
slower so we came to the conclusion that
慢一点，所以我们得出的结论是
if we try to split this into micro
如果我们尝试将其拆分为微型
services in some in some way maybe we
以某种方式提供服务也许我们
will at least be able to recruit more
至少能够招募更多
people but maybe we'll be able to
人，但也许我们能够
increase the velocity or at least
提高速度或至少
something that doesn't belong to the
不属于
bounded context of binary context for a
二进制上下文的有界上下文
monolith sounds funny if assuming that
如果假设那，巨石听起来很有趣
we talked about the model if we had so
我们曾经讨论过这个模型
whatever doesn't shouldn't be there in
任何不应该存在的地方
the monolith maybe we will write it as a
整体也许我们会将其写为
separate deployable unit so we sat down
独立的可部署单位，所以我们坐下来
and said okay let's consider that and
说好吧，让我们考虑一下，
maybe it's time to actually take a look
也许是时候去看看
at the tools that are out there we went
在那里的工具，我们去了
to different conferences we read
参加我们阅读的不同会议
articles we read books and it turned out
我们看书的文章，结果
that the de facto standard for doing
事实标准
micro services are the Netflix yeah to a
微服务是Netflix对
slightly bigger company than us yeah by
比我们大一点的公司
a couple of hundred thousand requests
十万个请求
per second so we
每秒，所以我们
the conclusion that okay let's check the
好的结论，让我们检查一下
what those are we did an analysis and we
我们做了哪些分析，我们
came to the conclusion that it's
得出的结论是
actually not very easy to configure them
实际上不是很容易配置它们
even right we had a spring application
就算我们有 Spring 申请
yeah so integration with Netflix tools
是的，因此可以与Netflix工具集成
weren't that easy so we thought that
并不是那么容易，所以我们认为
let's try to abstract it let's hide all
让我们尝试抽象它让我们隐藏所有
the details in some nice abstraction so
细节很好地抽象了
that the developers will not have to
开发人员将不必
actually you know play with
其实你知道玩
configuration of different tools within
内部不同工具的配置
them Netflix portfolio so we took a look
他们的Netflix投资组合，所以我们看看
at what's there and the OSS market and
在什么地方以及OSS市场以及
we found Spring Cup which was in
我们发现了 Spring 杯
snapshots like that of course with Olga
像Olga一样的快照
we've always done yellow driven
我们总是做黄驱动
development and we could have taken the
发展，我们本来可以
snapshots of a library but we are a
一个库的快照，但是我们是一个
little bit scared so we sat down and we
有点害怕，所以我们坐下来，我们
had this great absolutely brilliant idea
这个伟大的绝妙主意
that all of us have at certain point
我们所有人在某个时候都拥有
let's build something of our own so
让我们建立自己的东西
great idea is in the same month
好主意是在同一个月
absolutely so we did do that we built
绝对，所以我们做到了
something of Vernon but actually that
弗农的东西，但实际上
made sense because we needed a different
有道理，因为我们需要一个不同的
release cadence and we wanted those
释放节奏，我们想要那些
abstractions to be specific for our use
特定于我们使用的抽象
cases right so we did create such a tool
正确的案例，所以我们确实创建了这样的工具
we abstracted all sorts of things inside
我们提取了里面的各种东西
but you know time passed and spring
但是你知道时间过去了， Spring
clouds much to our surprise cups for us
为我们带来的惊喜杯
right and overtaking us in terms of the
权利并超越我们
features and and the quality especially
特点和质量
the colony and then we decided that ok
殖民地，然后我们决定确定
so since we are already experienced
所以既然我们已经经验丰富
developers we know that the best
开发人员我们知道最好
solution to any problem is to push this
解决任何问题的方法就是推这个
problem to somebody else right
对其他人的问题对
delegating delegation delegation is the
委托代表团代表团是
key so we said ok so no longer do we
关键，所以我们说好，所以我们不再
want to support our tools let's push
想要支持我们的工具，让我们推动
them to spring cloud so that's what we
他们到了 Spring ，这就是我们
did and a lot of stuff that is in spring
做了，很多东西在 Spring
cloud was since become like them at
云从此成为像他们一样
least in some projects or contributed by
至少在某些项目中或由
us because we wanted to delegate this
我们，因为我们想委托这个
problem to somebody else the problem was
别人的问题是
that due to the fact that we did it
由于我们做到这一点
we got hired by pivot oh so we delegated
我们被Pivot聘请了哦，所以我们委派了
to this prick our team so we delegated
为了给我们的团队带来好处，我们委托
our own problems to our cells so I guess
我们自己的问题给我们的细胞，所以我猜
we're back yeah anyways from then we
从那时起我们就回来了
started using spring cloud because it
开始使用Spring Cloud，因为它
allowed us to have very very very nice
让我们拥有非常非常非常好的
abstractions over various things which
对各种事物的抽象
are those for example from the Netflix
例如来自Netflix的
portfolio that's why we had the spring
这就是为什么我们有了 Spring
called Netflix Project heavily used in
叫做Netflix Project
in our project so what are those tools
在我们的项目中，那些工具是什么
so we had we have speak on Netflix
所以我们有在Netflix上发言
Eureka so who has heard of Eureka okay
尤里卡，所以谁听说尤里卡好
oh that's a lot of people so I'm not
哦，有很多人，所以我不是
gonna ask if you heard about service
会问你是否听说过服务
discovery because essentially Eureka is
发现，因为本质上尤里卡是
an implementation of the service
服务的实现
discovery tool for those who don't know
不认识的人的发现工具
because they were like two hands service
因为就像双手服务
discovery is a mechanism that within the
发现是一种机制，
cloud architecture you no longer
您不再需要的云架构
hard-code the IP and port but you ask a
对IP和端口进行硬编码，但您要求
an app a service like Eureka can you
像尤里卡这样的应用程序，您可以
give me the radicals can have multiple
给我自由基可以有多个
instances of an app deployed in the
部署在
cloud so that's Eureka
云，那是尤里卡
we have Arceus who has heard of our case
我们有听说过我们案子的阿尔修斯
who's using our case that's interesting
谁在使用我们的案例，这很有趣
okay there are some people so a lot of
好吧，有很多人
you are using it as a transitive
您正在使用它作为传递
dependency yeah so maybe I should have
是的，所以也许我应该有
asked who's using it by desire so they
问谁愿意使用它，所以他们
said so our caius it's a tool used for
说，所以我们的caius是用于
dynamic configuration like essentially
本质上是动态配置
ribbon I remember like five years ago
我记得五年前的缎带
when I first saw ribbon and I heard that
当我第一次看到丝带时，我听到
it's a client-side load balancer I
这是我的客户端负载均衡器
thought that it makes absolutely no
以为它绝对不会
sense like why would you use it if you
感觉就像你为什么要使用它
can have a lot of balancer but why would
可以有很多平衡器，但是为什么会
you have a client-side load balancer
您有一个客户端负载均衡器
what actually it makes a lot of sense
实际上有什么意义
because if you communicate with various
因为如果你与各种交流
apps you can have different you can
您可以拥有不同的应用程序
tweak the way you treat load balancing
调整处理负载平衡的方式
for that particular app another thing
对于那个特定的应用程序，另一件事
which is very interesting is what
很有意思的是
happens if you don't have a client-side
如果没有客户端，则会发生
load balancer that caches the I say the
负载均衡器缓存我说的
addresses of different apps in case
万一不同应用的地址
where the service discovery system goes
服务发现系统的去向
down right if it goes down you can ask
如果它掉下来，你可以问
for IPs and ports and you have a problem
对于IP和端口，您有问题
but if you cache you can have a snapshot
但是如果您缓存，可以拥有快照
of the world of course it can be updated
当然可以更新
but at least you have something right
但至少你有对的事
so that's ribbon dual who's using zoo
这就是谁正在使用动物园的功能区双
that's nice
真好
so zoo for those who don't use it it's a
所以对于那些不使用它的人来说，这是一个
proxy essentially hystrix who's using
代理本质上是谁使用的hystrix
histories okay that's a lot of people so
历史很好，很多人都这样
hystrix is an implementation of circuit
hystrix是电路的实现
breakers essentially we don't to
破坏者本质上我们不
propagate a cascade failure if one app
如果一个应用程序传播级联故障
is calling another for example and the
例如打电话给另一个
other app is malfunctioning at some
其他应用有些故障
point when some statistics will let's
指出何时一些统计数据可以让我们
say define it we assume that the other
说定义它，我们假设另一个
app is like we shouldn't call it because
应用程序就像我们不应该调用它，因为
it's gonna fail anyway so we can
无论如何都会失败，所以我们可以
short-circuit the calls we can say
短路我们可以说的电话
either immediately for an exception or
立即例外
return a fixed response right histories
返回固定的响应权历史
dashboard so this is a UI to visualize
仪表板，所以这是一个可视化的UI
the state of our systems in terms of the
我们系统的状态
circular breakers turbine if you have a
圆形断路器涡轮机（如果您有）
lot of apps that have circuit breakers
很多具有断路器的应用
you can aggregate them right and this
您可以正确地汇总它们，这
turbine is an aggregate so the last two
涡轮是一个集合，所以最后两个
apps are actually purely spring cloud
应用程序实际上纯粹是 Spring 的云
apps that allow you to gather data from
允许您从中收集数据的应用
hysterics and turbines via messaging by
歇斯底里和涡轮通过消息传递
a sprinkle stream so these were the
洒水流，所以这些是
abstraction that spring cloud has
Spring Cloud 具有的抽象
created and we continue to use them in
创建，我们将继续使用它们
our previous job and now we're
我们以前的工作，现在我们
developing them in spring club so you
在 Spring 俱乐部发展他们，所以你
know time flight everybody was happy
知道时间飞行每个人都很高兴
because you know Netflix they come to
因为你知道Netflix他们来了
write and they develop great software
写，他们开发了很棒的软件
everybody uses them what can shake yeah
每个人都用它们会震动什么
yeah apparently you could have seen how
是的，您显然已经看到了
many users were using that and then 2016
很多用户都在使用它，然后在2016年
comes and suddenly it turns out that
来了，突然发现
ribbon is going into maintenance mode
碳带进入维护模式
which means for Netflix we're not doing
这意味着对于Netflix，我们不会
anything with the project except for the
该项目的任何内容，除了
fact that if we as Netflix need
事实上，如果我们作为Netflix需要
something from the project we're going
我们要从项目中得到的东西
to do it but no issues will be fixed
做到这一点，但不会解决任何问题
we're not touching the project if you
如果您是我们，我们不会涉及该项目
don't have to which is kind of sad right
不必去那是一种可悲的权利
because a lot of people are using ribbon
因为很多人都在用色带
it's 2016 right so that's a lot of time
是2016年，所以很多时间
already there are companies that build
已经有公司在建
something on top of history dashboard
历史记录仪表盘上的内容
right too
也对
some stuff better suddenly the project
一些东西突然变得更好
is going into maintenance you have to
要进行维护，您必须
start using project atlas which is
开始使用项目图集
completely backwards incompatible with
完全向后兼容
hystrix data like zero Zul one you're
像零Zul一样的hystrix数据
using Zoli created some different routes
使用Zoli创建了一些不同的路线
customizations so tooth comes in
定制，使牙齿进来
completely backwards incompatible we
完全向后不兼容，我们
can't directly migrate you have to write
无法直接迁移，您必须编写
some stuff from scratch our case one our
从头开始一些东西我们的情况一我们
guys do the same thing and then the bomb
家伙做同样的事情，然后炸弹
hystrix 2018 not maintained anymore
hystrix 2018不再维护
right
对
so they also decided to delegate exactly
所以他们也决定完全委托
so is right because most likely it's
是对的，因为很可能是
just an assumption it might have
只是一个假设
something to do with the fact that
与以下事实有关
netflix has decided to go fully with
netflix已决定完全使用
spring boot and spring club and
spring boot 和 Spring 俱乐部和
yesterday a drink'll was giving a
昨天喝酒会给
presentation about distributed tracing
关于分布式跟踪的演示
so I was really happy like I was smiling
所以我真的很开心，就像我在微笑一样
because I saw that the tool that we're
因为我看到了我们所使用的工具
developing sprinkles oof is heavily used
显影剂大量使用
by Netflix which means that Netflix
Netflix的意思是Netflix
learned from us and decided to delegate
向我们学习并决定委托
their problems to us right so that makes
他们的问题对我们来说是正确的，这使得
sense
感
took them some time yeah so we also
花了一些时间是的，所以我们也
decided not to be worse than Netflix and
决定不比Netflix更差
we said we're going to go over
我们说我们要过去
maintenance mode as well so with
维护模式也是如此
Greenwich RC one we decided to go to
我们决定去的格林威治RC一
maintenance mode but it's a little bit
维护模式，但有点
different our maintenance mode to theirs
不同于我们的维护方式
because we say that ok here we agree
因为我们说好，我们同意
with Netflix no new features we're not
Netflix没有新功能，我们不是
adding any new features but if they're
添加任何新功能，但如果它们是
blockers or if there are security
阻止者或是否存在安全性
problems we will fix those right we will
问题，我们将解决这些问题，我们将
do we also love our community so we can
我们也爱我们的社区吗？
have a discussion and another one and
进行讨论，然后再讨论
ten more iterations and then if there's
再十次迭代，然后如果有
a small pool request will review it and
一个小的池请求将对其进行审核，
merge it right so it's it's a little bit
正确合并它，这是一点点
different so if you check this out all
不一样，所以如果您全部查看
the gray projects are going into
灰色项目正在进入
maintenance mode right so everything
维护模式正确，所以一切
except for Eureka was going in
除了尤里卡要进去
maintenance mode yeah
维护模式
yes it's already in maintenance mode
是的，它已经处于维护模式
since Greenwich rc1 and we have already
自格林威治rc1以来，我们已经
Greenwich a service released one so it
格林威治发布了一项服务，因此
was some time ago but Eureka is still at
是前一段时间，但尤里卡仍在
all so it's not going into maintenance
所有这一切都不需要维护
mode at all right now so right now we're
现在所有的模式
gonna show you I'm gonna show you the
要告诉你我要告诉你
old stack shrink on Netflix so you could
Netflix上的旧堆栈缩小，因此您可以
leverage that so we need that demo so we
利用它，因此我们需要该演示，因此我们
need some sort of a business domain so
需要某种业务领域，所以
we're at a conference so it has to be
我们正在开会，所以必须
either a beer or financial domain yeah
是啤酒还是金融领域
so let's go okay so we're gonna have a
所以我们走吧，我们要
user that registers for a credit card so
注册信用卡的用户
we're gonna have a card service some
我们要一些卡服务
processing goes on so we have to create
处理继续进行，因此我们必须创建
an user and we're gonna call a proxy or
用户，我们将呼叫代理或
via that proxy we'll call the user
通过该代理，我们将呼叫用户
service in order to create a new user
服务以创建新用户
and also there has to be a flood verify
而且还必须进行洪水验证
or always even if yeah so there's gonna
甚至总是，即使是的，所以
be also verification if there's a
还要验证是否有
there's a fraud
有欺诈
so the tactic we're gonna use is we're
所以我们要使用的策略是
gonna use in the card application
将在卡应用程序中使用
service we're gonna use ribbon as a
服务，我们将使用功能区作为
proxy we're gonna use this duel and we
代理，我们将使用这个决斗，我们
don't have hystrix in history dashboard
历史记录仪表盘中没有hystrix
there we're going to find all the
在那里我们将找到所有
applications using eureka right so
使用eureka的应用程序对吧
that's probably the starting stack is
那可能是起始堆栈
probably the one many of you absolutely
绝对是你们中的一员
you might be interested in the ignore it
您可能会对忽略它感兴趣
service all of us have this ignore
服务我们所有人都有这个忽略
service right typically it's a service
服务权通常是一项服务
on production that we have no code
在生产中我们没有代码
source for but it's running and nobody
源，但正在运行，没有人
wants to kill it right so this is one of
想杀死它，所以这是其中之一
the apps and the thing is that we want
应用程序，而事实是我们想要
to show you the difference between Zul
告诉你祖尔之间的区别
and the gateway and we've zoo everything
和门户，我们已经动物园了一切
is white listed so if we want to
是白色列出的，所以如果我们想
blacklist an app we have to explicitly
将我们必须明确列出的应用列入黑名单
do it so a blacklisted app is an ignored
这样做是为了将被列入黑名单的应用忽略
service yeah so that's why we called it
服务是的，所以这就是为什么我们叫它
and ignore it serves it makes sense
并忽略它是有道理的
right and there's going to be also
对，而且还会有
turbine application and we're gonna show
涡轮机的应用，我们将展示
you that so let's go to the code
你，让我们去看代码
we're in a proper place let's go from
我们在一个合适的地方，让我们从
the very very beginning so we have a
刚开始的时候，所以我们有一个
user service let's check out the user
用户服务，让我们签出用户
service so what do you have here we have
服务，所以您在这里有什么
the mouse in the other direction so we
鼠标在另一个方向上，所以我们
have user service application we are
有用户服务应用程序
enabling hystrix in history
在历史中启用hystrix
dashboard because we can so a request
仪表板，因为我们可以这样请求
comes in and we delegate the work to
进来，我们将工作委托给
user registration service whatever that
用户注册服务
is so now let's check out the user
现在是这样，让我们​​检查用户
registration service again we are very
再次登记服务，我们非常
good at delegation so we delegate from
擅长委派，所以我们从
user registration service to
用户注册服务
verification service quiet and now let's
验证服务安静，现在让我们
check this out so the first thing we can
检查一下，所以我们可以做的第一件事
see here is actually I should start with
看到这里实际上是我应该开始的
the cards card service sorry let's go
卡片服务抱歉，我们走吧
for the car service this is the last
对于汽车服务，这是最后一次
application let's start with the first
应用程序从第一个开始
so we have the card service application
所以我们有卡服务申请
sorry so let's start with the user
抱歉，让我们从用户开始
service client and here we are injecting
服务客户，我们在这里注入
a risk template so one of the most
风险模板，因此是最
frequent questions we had is if we are
我们经常遇到的问题是我们是否
using spring cloud and we have a risk
使用 Spring Cloud ，我们有风险
template one of which is an ordinary
模板之一是普通的
risk template and the other one is
风险模板，另一个是
supposed to be used in the load balancer
应该在负载均衡器中使用
way right so we need to find an
正确的方法，所以我们需要找到一个
application in service registry how can
服务注册表中的应用程序如何
we do it you can't even imagine how many
我们做到了，你甚至无法想象有多少
times have we heard this question so if
有时我们听到过这个问题，所以如果
you have this question we're going to
你有这个问题，我们要
answer it right now you have to use a
立即回答，您必须使用
qualifier so if we go to the
预选赛，所以如果我们去
configuration of our application we'll
配置我们的应用程序
see that we have to rest templates beans
看到我们必须休息模板 bean
one is load balanced which means that if
一个是负载均衡的，这意味着
we call a host with a given name that
我们使用给定名称的主机
name is going to be a service ID in
名称将是中的服务ID
eureka and the other one is an ordinary
尤里卡，另一个是普通人
ris template and you have the qualifiers
ris模板，您就有了限定词
that differentiate the two
区分两者
correct and here you can see the ribbon
正确，在这里您可以看到功能区
load balancer definition or
负载均衡器定义或
customization so they say how does it
定制，所以他们说怎么做
work I'm gonna show you in a second so
工作，我一秒钟会告诉你
let's go to the user service client so
让我们去用户服务客户端
we inject the rest template with
我们将其余模板注入
qualifiers template which is the Orden
资格赛模板是Orden
and here we have a very nice obstruction
在这里，我们有一个很好的障碍
go to Discovery client coming from
转到来自的发现客户端
spring cloud so what we do here is we
Spring 的云，所以我们在这里做的是
are searching for a service ID called
正在搜索名为
proxy and we're retrieving the instances
代理，我们正在检索实例
all the instances of those of this
这些的所有实例
particular service so if we go to if we
特殊的服务，所以如果我们去
go to the Eureka server you'll see that
转到Eureka服务器，您将看到
we have quite a few apps running here I
我们有很多应用程序在这里运行
don't need the mouse I have my two
不需要鼠标，我有两个
fingers here so here we have quite a few
手指在这里，所以在这里我们有很多
apps registers so card service for the
应用程序注册，以便为
verifier ignored and the proxy right so
验证程序被忽略，代理正确
if you do if we in the code say get
如果您这样做，如果我们在代码中说得到
instances of proxy we will retrieve
我们将检索的代理实例
those instances if there are none we're
那些实例，如果没有，我们就是
going to throw an exception so then what
会引发异常，那又怎样
we're doing is we're calling the proxy
我们正在做的是我们正在调用代理
with the user service registration path
用户服务注册路径
which means we're saying dear Zuul
这意味着我们在说亲爱的祖尔
please find user service and redirect
请找到用户服务并重定向
the call to user services registration
用户服务注册电话
and put so that's how you can do it with
并把它放进去，这样你就可以做到
a standard rest template now if we go to
现在，如果我们去一个标准的休息模板
the verification service client you will
您将使用的验证服务客户端
see that we're doing a load balance at
看到我们正在做负载均衡
load balancers template and here we're
负载均衡器模板，我们在这里
calling the fraud verifier hostname of
呼叫的欺诈验证者主机名
course there is no such a hostname but
当然没有这样的主机名，但是
since we're using ribbon underneath the
因为我们在下方使用色带
hostname will be converted into a
主机名将转换为
service ID and things will happen
服务ID，一切都会发生
because as Olga mentioned in the
因为正如奥尔加（Olga）在
configuration we have ribbon client and
配置我们有功能区客户端和
here we say there's a custom ribbon
这里我们说有一个自定义功能区
configuration so you annotate your class
配置，以便您注释课程
with ribbon client and you provide a
与功能区客户端，您提供
custom ribbon configuration here you can
您可以在此处自定义功能区配置
define that for this particular client
为此特定客户定义
so if we're calling the fraud detection
所以如果我们称欺诈检测
the the rule the load balancer rules
负载均衡器规则的规则
should be the round robin rule and you
应该是循环法则，而你
could create your own rules etc etcetera
可以创建自己的规则等
right so this is how you use tell ribbon
对，所以这就是你使用告诉功能区的方式
how to behave in a custom way so that
如何以自定义方式表现
was the card service now we let's go to
是卡服务，现在我们去
the proxy
代理
so the proxy has a single annotation in
因此代理在其中具有单个注释
terms of Zul which is enables a proxy
启用代理的Zul条款
you can see here and the whole
你可以看到这里和整个
configuration is there in the resources
资源中有配置
so we have Zul we say like I said
所以我们有祖尔，就像我说的那样
everything is white listed
一切都是白名单
so we say ignored services are those
所以我们说被忽略的服务是那些
that for example the ignored service so
例如被忽略的服务
the one whose service ID ignored but if
服务ID被忽略的那个，但是如果
you want to allow like white list the
你想允许像白名单
white was just a certain path you have
白色只是您的必经之路
to ignore it completely and white list a
完全忽略它，将白名单
given path for example tests allowed if
给定路径，例如允许的测试
you call any other path in the ignore
您在忽略中调用任何其他路径
service is not going to be you can
服务不会是你可以的
configure around six more things yeah so
配置大约六件事是的，所以
that that Zoo and last but not least
那个动物园，最后但并非最不重要的
let's go back to the user service and
让我们回到用户服务，
let's go over here so again like I
让我们再回到这里像我一样
mentioned we have a controller to
提到我们有一个控制器
delegates to a service to delegates to
代表服务
another service and let's focus on that
另一项服务，让我们专注于
one we have a rest template and
我们有一个休息模板，
discovery client and here you can see
发现客户端，在这里您可以看到
the historic schema
历史图式
right so you have a method called verify
正确，所以您有一个称为verify的方法
a new user we wrap it with a history
新用户，我们将其与历史记录一起包装
command which means that the result of
命令意味着结果
execution of this method will be
该方法的执行将是
measured right and if within certain
衡量是否正确
period of time we have X number of
一段时间我们有X个
exceptions hystrix will assume that the
异常hystrix将假定
other app is faulty and will not at
其他应用程式有毛病，不会在
certain point called the other
某个点称为另一个
application it will throw an exception
应用程序将引发异常
in this case we have a fallback method
在这种情况下，我们有一个后备方法
which means that if there is a problem
这意味着如果有问题
we will have the user rejected method
我们将有用户拒绝的方法
execute it which will assume that all of
执行它会假设所有
the users are frauds right so that's
用户是欺诈行为，因此
pretty much it let's check out what we
差不多，让我们看看我们
have here we're gonna send some requests
在这里，我们要发送一些请求
so we're doing we're sending a lot of
所以我们正在做很多事情
requests let's go to the to our
请求让我们去我们的
application and using a B which is a
应用程序并使用B
nice benchmarking tool yeah so we're
不错的基准测试工具，是的，我们
sending all sorts of applications a
发送各种应用程序
source of requests and here we can see
请求的来源，在这里我们可以看到
history dashboard which shows us the
历史仪表板向我们展示了
state of our commands in the system
我们命令在系统中的状态
hopefully you can see that there's a
希望你能看到有一个
green the circle is quite big because
绿色的圆圈很大，因为
there's a gigantic load we should be
我们应该有一个巨大的负担
getting down because we stopped doing
下山，因为我们停止做
any calls circuits are closed which
任何呼叫电路均已关闭
means that everything is fine there are
意味着一切都很好
no red digits anywhere which means that
任何地方都没有红色数字，这意味着
there are no exceptions
没有例外
and here you can see the verifying user
在这里您可以看到验证用户
which
哪一个
means that this is the command that we
意味着这是我们的命令
wrapped in you know execution of our
包裹在你知道我们的执行
method so this is pretty much it in
方法，所以这差不多
terms of the old stack olga so maybe you
老堆栈奥尔加的条款，所以也许你
will tell us how to Mike yeah let's turn
会告诉我们如何迈克耶
to migrate to the new thing yeah I will
迁移到新事物，是的，我会
move to the right okay so that was just
移到右边好吧，那只是
the old stack and now let's see what can
旧堆栈，现在让我们看看可以
we do right now to stop working on this
我们现在要做停止这项工作
stock that is already under maintenance
已经维护的库存
so the first thing is the load balancer
所以第一件事是负载均衡器
so first things first let me just kill
所以首先要让我杀了
all these apps that are currently
目前所有这些应用
running so even using the old stack in a
运行，即使使用旧堆栈
similar way actually even though we just
实际上，即使我们只是
you know code the tools we still know
你知道编码我们仍然知道的工具
how to use it from right just quite good
如何正确地使用它
and let's just run the new stack so we
让我们运行新的堆栈，这样我们
are going to have the same functionality
将具有相同的功能
exactly in the same UPS but what we are
完全在同一台UPS中，但我们是
not going to do is we're going to try
不会做的是我们要尝试
and avoid the maintenance mode projects
并避免维护模式项目
so let's go here
所以我们去这里
okay let's start with our verification
好，让我们从验证开始
client so we had a load balance risk
客户，所以我们有负载平衡风险
template here and if you if we go to the
模板，如果您愿意，请转到
configuration part we will see that
配置部分，我们将看到
there were some changes so let's see the
发生了一些变化，让我们看看
country as you can see here not a lot
您在这里看到的国家不多
has changed let me close this for now so
已经改变了，让我暂时关闭它，所以
the real only thing that has changed in
真正改变的唯一事物
the code is this annotation so we had
代码是这个注释，所以我们有
written client now we'll have load
书面客户，现在我们要负担
balancer client and whatever we had
平衡客户以及我们拥有的一切
written clients we can now pass more
书面客户，我们现在可以通过更多
configuration also with load balancer
负载均衡器也可配置
clients now as you can see I have also
您现在看到的客户我也
switched to a reactive web communication
切换到反应式Web通讯
implementation so we are using web
实施，所以我们正在使用网络
client instead of rest template and I
客户而不是其余的模板，我
have done it on purpose the reason is
故意这样做的原因是
that right now at this moment this
此时此刻
annotation only works with reactive
注释仅适用于反应式
reactive stack but do not worry as we
反应堆，但不要担心，因为我们
will release Hoxton it will also work
将释放霍克斯顿，它也将工作
for non reactive stack so and that's the
对于非反应堆，那就是
thing you're doing and then we have load
你正在做的事情，然后我们有负担
balance again this will work same with
再次平衡，将与
web client build as it did with rest
Web客户端的构建与休息时一样
template and ideally what we would like
模板，理想情况下是我们想要的
to have is having new load balancer
拥有新的负载均衡器
triggered by it so right now what will
因此，它现在触发了什么
happen until now is you will have ribbon
发生直到现在是你将有功能区
trigger both for the reactive stack and
触发反应堆和
a non reactive start and especially with
无反应的开始，尤其是
the reactive start it's a problem
反应式启动是个问题
because it will be blocking us but this
因为它将阻止我们，但这
is something that the team has already
是团队已经拥有的东西
started working on so we have a new load
开始工作，所以我们有了新的负担
balancer spring controlled balancer and
平衡器Spring 控制平衡器和
now we have round-robin implementation
现在我们有了循环执行
this is a reactive implementation so
这是一个被动的实现，所以
what we are going to do for Hoxton again
我们将再次为霍克斯顿做些什么
is that when you annotate your web
是当您注释网络时
client builder we have load balanced
客户端构建器，我们负载均衡
that reactive implementation will be
反应性实施将是
used underneath and you will not have to
在下面使用，您将不必
be blocked same we will also make a non
被阻止一样，我们也将使
reactive implementation and we will stop
反应性实施，我们将停止
using ribbon so this is a teaser there
用丝带，这是一个预告片
is some work to be done on our side
在我们这边要做的一些工作
third part is you don't need to change
第三部分是你不需要改变
practically anything you if you change
几乎所有你改变的东西
these annotations to obstructions so
这些对障碍物的注释
using load balancer crying and not
使用负载均衡器哭泣而不是
ribbon grinds you can still use the load
色带研磨仍可以使用负载
balanced annotation and all the work
平衡注释和所有工作
will be done underneath that our top
将在我们的顶下完成
priority for the next few months and we
接下来几个月的优先事项，我们
will be releasing this in Hoxton and we
将会在Hoxton发布，我们
will also be changing all the ribbon
也将改变所有的功能区
transitive dependencies switching to our
传递依赖切换到我们
own load balancer so essentially what we
自己的负载均衡器
want to do what we're trying to achieve
想要做我们想实现的目标
is the same user experience so to say as
是相同的用户体验，可以这么说
we have this discovery client right so
我们有这个发现客户，所以
we just change the jars from one
我们只是把罐子换成一个
discovery service to another like from
发现服务到另一个像
Eureka to zookeeper and you can you
尤里卡动物园管理员，你可以
don't have to change the code and we
不必更改代码，我们
would like to achieve the same thing in
想要在
terms of load balancing that it's purely
纯粹是负载均衡的术语
abstracted yeah so that's the first
是抽象的，所以这是第一个
change this change will happen mainly
改变，这种改变将主要发生
underneath now this is another change
现在这是另一个变化
and this will require some work on your
这将需要您的一些工作
part so that will be different but I
部分，所以会有所不同，但我
still think it's awesome because as you
仍然认为这很棒，因为就像你
will see it's going to be a fun project
将会看到这将是一个有趣的项目
to work with at least for me much more
至少与我合作
interesting to work with them and they
与他们一起工作很有趣，他们
pay us for fun right so let's do it
付钱给我们，好吧，让我们做吧
so you will have to change for Gateway
因此您必须更改网关
and how do you do it it's very easy
以及如何做到这一点非常容易
we of course fully support the spring
我们当然会全力支持 Spring
good model of making applications we
制作应用程序的良好模型
just need to add this starter and that's
只需添加此启动器，那就是
pretty much it now spring cloud gateway
现在几乎是 Spring Cloud 网关
is reactive so we absolutely do not
是反应性的，所以我们绝对不会
recommend trying to put the starter in
建议尝试将启动器放入
you're removing Zul dependency from your
你正在从你的祖尔消除依赖
nonreactive up and just substituting it
无反应的，只用它代替
no you should make another service and
不，您应该提供其他服务，
then even though this will be reactive
即使这是反应性的
you will be able to make calls from any
您将可以通过任何方式拨打电话
service you have can be spring MVC and
您可以使用的服务可以是Spring MVC和
be web client this will be a separate
是网络客户端，这将是一个单独的
app where you will be making calls
您将在其中拨打电话的应用程序
because if you try to add this reactive
因为如果您尝试添加此反应式
starter somewhere where you have non
初学者在您没有的地方
reactive spring both web starters it
无功Spring 两个幅面启动器
won't fail the second you mentioned that
你提到的那一秒钟不会失败
it's a built on top of reactor so do I
它是建在反应堆顶部的
have to know project reactors let you
必须知道项目反应堆让您
use it oh because
用哦，因为
you are just going to be directing calls
你只是要指挥电话
to the Gateway up and your other apps
到网关以及您的其他应用
can be written differently it's not
可以写成不同的不是
important so you media set the starter
重要，因此您可以设置启动器
and we have one neuron started that I
我们有一个神经元开始
want to show you which will show soon
想告诉你这将很快显示
what they do so we are reading actuator
他们在做什么，我们正在阅读执行器
and we are reading micrometer registry
我们正在阅读千分尺注册表
Prometheus these are optional that will
普罗米修斯这些是可选的
work without them and that's our gateway
没有他们就可以工作，这就是我们的门户
up so as you can see not much magic here
这样您就可以看到这里没有太多魔术了
now let's see where interesting thing
现在让我们看看有趣的地方
starts so in zone we could configure
开始，所以在区域中，我们可以配置
some things here we can configure much
这里有些事情我们可以配置很多
more I will start with Yama
我将从雅马开始
do not worry please do not leave just
别担心，请不要只留下
because you see this Yama config you
因为您看到这个Yama配置
will be able to do it differently I'm
我将能够以不同的方式来做
pretty sure they already work with
很确定他们已经与
kubernetes so they are familiar with
kubernetes，以便他们熟悉
IANA development ok yeah so as you can
IANA开发好的，所以您可以
see in gateway unlocking zone
在网关解锁区域中查看
so in zone we had all the routes
所以在区域中，我们拥有所有路线
configured for us implicitly and on one
为我们隐式配置
hand that was less work to do but on the
减少工作量的手
other hand that was quite unsafe from
另一方面是非常不安全的
security view you for now is not the
您目前的安全性视图不是
best solution because you could easily
最佳解决方案，因为您可以轻松地
again fail to add this ignored services
再次无法添加此被忽略的服务
that marching has shown and you would be
游行表明，你会
directing whatever you don't want to
指导你不想做的事
redirect so here it's explicit also if
重定向，所以这里也是显式的
you have any junior developers working
您有任何初级开发人员在工作
with you they will not be just sitting
和你在一起，他们不会只是坐在
and looking and thinking how the CAC is
并思考并思考CAC的方式
it being routed like what is happening
它像正在发生的那样被路由
now everything will be explicit and
现在一切都将是明确的，
wishing it's better this way so that's
希望这样更好，所以
why we switch to this mode so you will
为什么我们切换到此模式，以便您
have routes and for every route you will
有路线，您会为每条路线
have to define an ID and URI where you
必须在其中定义一个ID和URI
want to direct it and predicate so
想要指挥它并断言是这样
predicates will be conditions whenever a
谓词将成为条件，只要
request matches certain set of
请求与某组匹配
conditions we will direct it through
条件，我们将通过它
these filters so here we want to direct
这些过滤器，所以在这里我们要指导
everything that starts with slash fraud
以斜杠欺诈开头的一切
such a spread - verifier to load balance
如此分散-验证负载平衡
float verifier so we can ever had a
浮动验证程序，因此我们可以
direct
直接
HTTP pass or HTTPS but we can also just
HTTP pass或HTTPS，但我们也可以
start with Elbe and just only adding
从易北河开始，只添加
this Elbe scheme what we'll do is that
这个易北河计划，我们要做的是
we will use a load balancer underneath
我们将在下面使用负载均衡器
to connect to your service discovery and
连接到您的服务发现和
to resolve this service and then we are
解决这项服务，然后我们
using filters filters will allow you to
使用过滤器过滤器将使您能够
modify your request and your responses
修改您的请求和回复
and as you will see it you will be able
如您所见，您将能够
to do a huge amount of stuff of it that
做大量的事情
you were not able to do it so so here we
您无法执行此操作，所以在这里我们
just want to strip the prefix because
只想删除前缀，因为
once we redirect to the throat via fire
一旦我们通过火重定向到喉咙
app we don't have all our endpoints
应用我们没有我们所有的端点
starting with fraud verifier so we just
从欺诈验证者开始，所以我们只是
strip one part also just by adding only
也仅通过添加仅剥离一部分
this much config we have added a retry
这个配置太多，我们添加了一个重试
filter so we'll try trying three times
过滤器，因此我们将尝试尝试三遍
if anything fails and here is our
如果有任何失败，这是我们的
ignored service so here we used
忽略了服务，所以我们在这里使用
wildcards and we were directing
通配符，我们正在指导
everything starting with fraud verifier
一切始于欺诈验证者
to that service and here we are only
到该服务，这里我们只是
allowing one endpoint nothing else will
允许一个端点没有别的
be magically redirected and you will not
神奇地重定向，您将不会
have security bridge because of that so
因此有安全桥
that was the conservative way of
那是保守的方式
configuring it now let's go with the
现在配置它，让我们开始吧
more modern solution so now actually to
更现代的解决方案，所以现在实际上
have these routes you don't need to use
有这些路线，您不需要使用
the ml config you can just use Java code
您可以只使用Java代码的ml配置
config and the way you do it is you can
配置和你做的方式是你可以
define a being of type route locator and
定义路径定位器类型的存在，并
here you will have your routes and the
在这里，您将拥有自己的路线和
fun part is that we have this fluent API
有趣的是，我们有这个流利的API
so you can easily add stuff and as you
这样您就可以轻松添加内容
see here we also have a path predicate
看到这里我们还有一个路径谓词
but we are also adding a method
但我们也增加了一种方法
predicate so we will only want things
谓词，所以我们只会想要东西
that I will post method and we can add
我将发布方法，我们可以添加
more of them so we can add a lot you can
他们更多，所以我们可以添加很多你可以
check by URI you can use time time zones
通过URI检查您可以使用时区
for example you can use that before when
例如，您可以在
something happens in this time slot we
在这个时间段发生了一些事情
want to be direct here and in another
想要在这里和另一个地方直接
time slot we want to redirect something
我们想要重定向的时间段
somewhere else for example if we are
例如在其他地方
changing the topology of our
改变我们的拓扑
architecture that's very useful we can
我们可以非常有用的架构
use host predicates
使用主机谓词
can use after time three decades there's
可以在三十年后使用
a lot of options to look at and there's
有很多可供选择的选择，
a part where there is even much more you
有更多你的一部分
can do which is the filters so again you
可以做的是过滤器，所以再次
have the fluent API and you have the IDE
拥有流畅的API，并且拥有IDE
telling you what you can do and you can
告诉你你可以做什么，你可以
do pretty much anything so for example
做几乎任何事情，例如
you can set status you can add request
您可以设置状态可以添加请求
headers you can add parameters you can
标头可以添加参数
add response headers you can change the
添加响应头，您可以更改
requests your eyes you can even modify
要求你的眼睛，你甚至可以修改
the request body and the response body
请求主体和响应主体
so with the requests that are coming to
所以随着即将到来的请求
you and with the responses that you are
您以及您的回应
getting while you are routing them you
在路由他们时得到
can also do whatever you want you can
也可以做任何你想做的事
modify them and yeah everything is
修改它们，是的，一切都是
happening in a reactive way yeah
以反应的方式发生
actually I don't need to have any
其实我不需要任何东西
knowledge whatsoever about reactor to
关于反应堆的知识
use this you just call the methods and
使用它，您只需调用方法并
you will have the ideal telling you what
您将有理想告诉您什么
you can call and I have checked it so
你可以打电话，我已经检查过了
now we have more than twenty filters
现在我们有二十多个过滤器
available and if you think there is
可用，如果您认为有
something you absolutely need to have
你绝对需要的东西
and it's not there and it will be useful
它不在那里，将很有用
for everyone if you make an issue on
对于每个人，如果您在
github there is big chest will consider
github有很大的胸口会考虑
it so yeah very elastic way of working
是的，非常弹性的工作方式
with requests when compared to zoo now
与现在的动物园相比有要求
let's go further the other thing that we
让我们更进一步
should probably change is hystrix
应该改变的是hystrix
so I don't know about you but for me if
所以我不认识你，但对我来说
Netflix is not telling to use hystrix
Netflix不告诉使用hystrix
anymore and if Netflix is recommending
还有，如果Netflix建议
using resilience poojas
使用弹性poojaís
I guess it's better to do what they are
我想最好做他们自己的事
doing and switch to visitors or J so
并切换到访客或J这样
let's have a look at this but of course
让我们看看这个，当然
we could just tell you remove the
我们可以告诉您删除
history dependency add resilience for J
历史依赖关系为J添加弹性
I set it up and use it but then we would
我设置并使用它，但是我们会
be probably out of job because our job
可能因为我们的工作而失业
is to provide integrations so we won't
是为了提供集成，所以我们不会
do any I don't like it yeah so let's
做任何我不喜欢的事吧，让我们
provide the integration and that
提供整合，并且
something the team has done so we want
团队所做的事情，所以我们想要
you to be able just to add a starter
您就可以添加一个启动器
let's see this
让我们看看这个
close to many windows and if we see this
靠近许多窗户，如果我们看到这个
is our starter and you have to choose
是我们的入门者，您必须选择
the version you want snap shots
您想要快照的版本
sprinkler starter circuit breakers and
洒水起动器断路器和
I'm choosing resilience for J and we
我为J选择弹性，我们
have snapshots the reason is this is in
有快照的原因是
the incubator so this is an incubator
孵化器，所以这是一个孵化器
project but again as we reduce Hawkstone
项目，但随着我们减少Hawkstone
this will be reduced so this will be a
这将减少，所以这将是一个
production feature and let me show you
生产功能，让我向您展示
the way it works so we have done all the
它的工作方式，所以我们已经完成了所有
conflict for you and what you can do is
对你有冲突，你能做的是
just inject a beam a circuit breaker
只是向断路器注入光束
factory beam and then you can use it
工厂光束，然后就可以使用
instead of history's commands so let's
而不是历史命令，所以让我们
see the way we can use it we are using
看看我们使用它的方式
it here and previously with the history
它在这里和以前的历史
command it would wrap the entire method
命令它将包装整个方法
if you use the annotation all the calls
如果您使用注释，则所有调用
would be done within that histories
将在那个历史中完成
command but I am not really anticipating
命令，但我并不是很期待
having a lot of trouble setting query
设置查询有很多麻烦
parameters here or building the you
参数在这里或建立你
arise so I only want to wrap the actual
出现，所以我只想包装实际
call that I'm making which is here so I
叫我正在做的东西在这里，所以我
run create and I create a new circuit
运行create，然后创建一个新电路
with an ID and and then we call the
使用ID，然后我们将
method run where we can pass a lambda
在可以传递lambda的地方运行方法
with the actual execution that we want
与我们想要的实际执行
to do so that's the rest template part
这样做是剩下的模板部分
of course you could also use web client
当然，您也可以使用网络客户端
that would work both ways and then we
这将同时起作用，然后我们
pass another lambda of what to do and we
通过另一个做什么的lambda，我们
have a throwable so actually what we are
有一个可扔的东西，所以实际上我们是
passing is the call to this method if we
如果我们通过传递是对此方法的调用
get an exception we want to have a
得到一个例外，我们想要一个
fallback so that's the old good fall
后退，所以这是旧的好秋天
back is just not in an annotation it's
back不在注释中
just written directly programmatically
只是直接以编程方式编写
and this is a very simple way of using
这是一种非常简单的使用方法
it and actually let's let's run some
它，实际上让我们运行一些
calls why not let it start doing
打电话为什么不让它开始做
something
某事
yeah so in the meantime let's see the
是的，在此期间，让我们看看
other thing as you remember we had this
您记得的另一件事是我们有这个
history dashboard and it looked pretty
历史仪表板，看起来很漂亮
nice you could say at least for the time
不错，你至少可以说一遍
when it was made that seemed like a nice
当它看起来像一个不错的
UI but I don't know about you the main
用户界面，但我不了解您的主要信息
problem I had with that was why do I
我遇到的问题是为什么我
have all my metrics somewhere and all my
将我所有的指标都放在某个地方
dashboard somewhere and then only the
仪表板，然后只有
history dashboard using some other tools
使用其他工具的历史记录仪表板
something else not aggregated like why
其他没有聚合的东西，为什么
so what we think you might do and change
所以我们认为您可能会做并改变
not only your history dashboard but also
不仅是您的历史记录仪表板，还是
introduce as a pattern if you are not
如果你不是的话，作为一种模式介绍
collecting metrics by now you should
现在您应该收集指标
absolutely start doing it is to use a
绝对开始做的是使用
metric tool so the one we recommend for
公制工具，因此我们建议
our stock is micrometer and then you can
我们的存货是千分尺，那么您可以
use an aggregation tool and a
使用汇总工具和
dashboarding tool of choice so in this
选择的仪表板工具如此
presentation will be showing Prometheus
演示文稿将显示普罗米修斯
and Ravana but this is optional
和Ravana，但这是可选的
micrometer supports many tools so let's
千分尺支持许多工具，所以让我们
see it let's hope we got some calls at
看到它，希望我们能打来电话
this point let's see what's happening so
这一点让我们看看发生了什么
this is our dashboard and the front part
这是我们的仪表板和前部
here is that you can see the Gateway
这是您可以看到网关
dashboard and here for example you can
仪表板，例如
see request to given services and ok we
查看对给定服务的请求，好的，我们
cannot see it because it's the
无法看到它，因为它是
resolution doesn't show us but here I'm
分辨率不显示给我们，但我在这里
collecting successful requests to two
收集成功的请求给两个
different services via gateway but in
通过网关但在不同的服务
gateway I haven't added any meters or
网关我没有添加任何仪表或
any explicit matrix code only by adding
任何显式矩阵代码只能通过添加
the Prometheus registry and then by
Prometheus注册表，然后按
adding actuator we are getting
添加执行器
automatically by default a lot of
自动默认很多
metrics about our course and our
关于我们的课程和我们的指标
routings collected for gateway and then
为网关收集的路由，然后
you can use this data to create all your
您可以使用此数据创建所有
own dashboards so I'm not really a -
自己的仪表板，所以我不是-
boarding master you can create really
您可以真正创建的登机大师
nice crazy dashboards and the data is
不错的疯狂仪表板，数据是
here that's what I want to show you that
这就是我想告诉你的
you don't really need to add
您真的不需要添加
meters to Gateway for example and here
例如，到网关的米
is another one which is from our history
是我们历史上的另一个
that what was our history's execution
那是我们历史的死刑
and now is our new circuit breaker
现在是我们的新断路器
resilience poor J execution so what we
弹性差的J执行力，那么我们
have here is we can inject also a meter
这里有我们也可以注入仪表
object and we can use yeah so we can
对象，我们可以使用，所以我们可以
inject our meter registry and then we
注入我们的电表注册表，然后我们
can create whichever Mitch metric
可以创建任何米奇度量
objects we need and then we can use them
我们需要的对象，然后我们可以使用它们
as we would normally use them and
就像我们通常使用它们一样
they're already prepared for us they're
他们已经为我们做好了准备
auto configured for us so we don't need
为我们自动配置，因此我们不需要
to do it on our own
靠我们自己做
and as you see our circuit breaker going
如您所见，我们的断路器正在运行
back to this we can not only use it
回到这个我们不仅可以使用它
straight ahead over that works we can
直接进行这项工作，我们可以
also customize it so in order to make it
也要对其进行自定义以便制作
easy for you we have prepared this
方便您，我们已经准备好了
option that you can define customizer
您可以定义定制程序的选项
beings of a given time
给定时间的生物
type so as we are working with
输入，以便我们与之合作
resilience for J that's the resilience
J的弹性就是弹性
Forge a circuit breaker factory and you
打造断路器工厂，您
can configure whatever you could
可以配置任何您可以
normally configure for your zillions for
通常为您配置成千上万的
J so here for example we are just
J所以例如在这里我们只是
passing some time limiter config changes
通过一些时间限制器配置更改
and then we are using the defaults but
然后我们使用默认值
if you go to this class it is actually a
如果你去这堂课，那实际上是
builder so it allows you very easily to
生成器，因此它使您非常轻松地
adjust whatever is that you could
调整您可以做的一切
possibly adjust for resilience for J so
可能会调整J的弹性
that's the circuit breaker let's go back
那是断路器，让我们回去
to the presentation there is one more
到演示文稿还有一个
thing that you absolutely should be
你绝对应该的东西
changing while going forward and this is
在前进的过程中改变，这是
something we will not be showing in the
我们不会在其中显示的东西
demo because of two reasons so if you
演示有两个原因，所以如果您
are still using directly I mean not as
仍在直接使用，我的意思不是
transitive dependency this way a lot of
这种方式的传递依赖
you is used are using it and you don't
您习惯使用它，而您不
probably even know but if you're using
可能甚至知道，但是如果您正在使用
directly spring cloud Netflix archives
直接发布云Netflix档案
it's really hard time to switch to
真的很难切换到
sprinkler config server and we will not
喷头配置服务器，我们不会
be showing this because first of all as
之所以显示这一点，是因为首先
we have seen
我们已经看到
very little people use it directly and
很少有人直接使用它，
second because sprinkler config server
第二，因为喷水灭火配置服务器
has been with us for many years there
已经和我们在一起了很多年
are a lot of presentations about it
关于它的很多介绍
there's a lot of dogs but if you're
有很多狗，但是如果你是
using our Caius it's time to switch so
使用我们的Caius，是时候切换了
here we have seen how it could go for
在这里，我们已经看到了
the old Netflix based stuff to the new
从旧的基于Netflix的东西到新的
spring cloud recommended stack so we
Spring 的云推荐堆栈，所以我们
have changed to load balancer client
已更改为负载均衡器客户端
abstractions from ribbon clients we have
我们拥有的功能区客户端的抽象
stopped using hystrix and instead using
停止使用hystrix，而是使用
resilience 4j via the spring cloud
通过Spring 云恢复4j
circuit breaker project we have started
我们已经开始的断路器项目
using micrometer also for our history
使用千分尺也是我们的历史
our resilience project commands
我们的弹性项目命令
executions and we have switched from zoo
处决，我们已经从动物园换了
to gateway and we have kept eureka
到网关，我们保留了尤里卡
service discovery that's not in
不在的服务发现
maintenance for now there is no reason
目前没有任何维护
to switch from it if you were happy with
如果满意的话可以从中切换
using it so should you be making the
使用它，所以你应该使
change as we announced this with our z1
随着我们用z1宣布这一点而改变
that was January of this year and we
那是今年一月，我们
said that we will keep these projects in
说我们将保留这些项目
maintenance mode and we would continue
维护模式，我们将继续
maintaining them for at least one year
维持至少一年
so if you have a short lift up or one
所以如果你举起一小段时间
that will be decommissioned and will not
将会退役，不会
go further than one year
超过一年
you shouldn't probably change that would
你不应该改变那会
be a waste of time and any other case
浪费时间和其他任何情况
the time is now because even though we
现在是因为即使我们
will still be maintaining it for at
仍将维持在
least one year you should probably be
至少应该是一年
thinking about the change so first of
首先考虑变化
all why I would recommend switching to
所有为什么我建议切换到
gateway because that's already
网关，因为那已经
production already switching to
生产已经切换到
micrometer and then when Hoxton gets
千分尺，然后当霍克斯顿
released
已发布
switching to circuit breaker and also
切换到断路器
doing the load balancer changes so
进行负载平衡器更改后，
basically switching to abstractions and
基本上切换到抽象和
as I said there are still some changes
就像我说的还有一些变化
that we need to do on our part so you
我们需要做的，所以你
can be sure that we will not stop
可以确保我们不会停止
maintaining those projects and until our
维护那些项目，直到我们
substitute are completely ready but yeah
替代品已经完全准备好了，但是
as Hoxton Hoxton release train gets
随着霍克斯顿霍克斯顿释放火车得到
released by us you should probably be
由我们发布，您可能应该
making the change
做出改变
and for Gateway and micrometer I would
对于网关和千分尺，我会
recommend it now and of course for
现在推荐它，当然
convicts error so that's the timeline
定罪，因此是时间表
possible issues as I said we don't have
我说过的可能的问题
it already yet so the transition would
它还没有，所以过渡会
have to be gradual but we will make sure
必须是渐进的，但我们会确保
that everything is ready before we
在我们准备好一切之前
completely stop maintaining spring cloud
完全停止维护Spring 云
Netflix stock and this project has a
Netflix股票，该项目有一个
demo called there is you can check it in
演示那里有你可以签入
github we will also publish our slides
github我们还将发布我们的幻灯片
and we have some time for questions do
我们有一些时间来提问
you have any questions so the question
你有任何问题，所以这个问题
was if for the Gateway we still support
如果我们仍然支持网关
the spring security integration yes and
Spring Security 集成是和
there is a sample if you see our spring
有一个样品，如果你看到我们的 Spring
cloud samples of setting it up with all
全部设置的云样本
- as I remember you said you have
-我记得你说过
already 20 filters in the Gateway yeah
网关中已经有20个过滤器了
and is it possible to add some custom
并可以添加一些自定义
ones like Enzo yes yes you can also
像恩佐这样的人，是的，你也可以
implement the customer is essentially
实现客户本质上
it's an interface right that you have -
这是您拥有的界面权利-
I think there was a question there
我认为那里有一个问题
if I'm deploying my application on
如果我将应用程序部署在
kubernetes does it make sense to use
kubernetes是否有意义
client-side discovery and load balancing
客户端发现和负载平衡
what I have already services yes so yeah
我已经提供的服务是的，是的
because I mean I'm gonna answer like a
因为我的意思是我要像
consultant it depends
顾问取决于
yeah I mean of course kubernetes gives
是的，我当然是说kubernetes给
you the lezzy load balancing on on its
您在其庞大的负载平衡上
side right because for example you can
右边，因为例如
hide X number of pods under the same
隐藏相同数量的X个 bean 荚
label and just references via a single
标签和仅通过单个引用
service and it's gonna you know a little
服务，你会知道一点
balance it you can however have custom
平衡它，但是您可以自定义
strategy of load balancing on the client
客户端负载均衡策略
side it's not mandatory to do it but you
这不是强制性的，但是你
can do it right
可以做对
also remember that for example if you're
还请记住，例如，如果您
using spring cloud kubernetes as a
使用Spring Cloud Kubernetes作为一个
library you still leverage the same
库您仍然利用相同的
abstractions that are there in say
可以说的抽象
spring cloud as such so we do have load
这样的 Spring Cloud ，所以我们确实有负载
balancer and you can use ribbon to say
平衡器，您可以使用功能区说
fetch the the instances from kubernetes
从kubernetes获取实例
right so it's like the implementation of
对，所以就像实施
how you fetch the data is not like go to
您如何获取数据不像去
Eureka and fetch the instances from
尤里卡并从中获取实例
Eureka but fetch it from kubernetes
尤里卡（Eureka），但可从kubernetes获取
right and then you can apply custom
对，然后您可以应用自定义
strategies but it's it's up to you right
策略，但这取决于您自己
if if you don't have such a need you
如果您没有这样的需要
don't have to do it
不必这样做
so the question was if we're going to
所以问题是我们是否要
support the annotation based model for
支持基于注释的模型
circuit breakers there is an issue and
断路器有问题，
depending on the scale of interest in
取决于兴趣的规模
the community of having this feature the
具有此功能的社区
decision will be taken so I guess if
将会做出决定，所以我想如果
everyone wants it probably added as of
每个人都希望它可能已添加
now we haven't received enough support
现在我们还没有得到足够的支持
for this feature to implement it so the
为此功能实施
answer is it depends yes all right
答案是，取决于是否可以
any more questions so there are no more
还有更多问题，所以没有更多
questions so if you're shy you can come
问题，所以如果你害羞，你可以来
to us and we'll answer those questions
给我们，我们将回答这些问题
and if not thank you very much
如果不是的话，非常感谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]